{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943324366","data":{"timestamp":" 946943324365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943326499","data":{"timestamp":" 946943326498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943328652","data":{"timestamp":" 946943328651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943331870","data":{"timestamp":" 946943331868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943334118","data":{"timestamp":" 946943334117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943336324","data":{"timestamp":" 946943336323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943339137","data":{"timestamp":" 946943339136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943341298","data":{"timestamp":" 946943341298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943343435","data":{"timestamp":" 946943343435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943346659","data":{"timestamp":" 946943346655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943348792","data":{"timestamp":" 946943348792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943350903","data":{"timestamp":" 946943350903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943353907","data":{"timestamp":" 946943353906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943356136","data":{"timestamp":" 946943356134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943358390","data":{"timestamp":" 946943358389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943361446","data":{"timestamp":" 946943361445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943363831","data":{"timestamp":" 946943363830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943366173","data":{"timestamp":" 946943366172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943369222","data":{"timestamp":" 946943369221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943371402","data":{"timestamp":" 946943371402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943373564","data":{"timestamp":" 946943373564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943376692","data":{"timestamp":" 946943376692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943378887","data":{"timestamp":" 946943378887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943381082","data":{"timestamp":" 946943381081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943384236","data":{"timestamp":" 946943384235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943386677","data":{"timestamp":" 946943386676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943389114","data":{"timestamp":" 946943389114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943392274","data":{"timestamp":" 946943392273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943394545","data":{"timestamp":" 946943394544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943396805","data":{"timestamp":" 946943396805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943399811","data":{"timestamp":" 946943399811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943402018","data":{"timestamp":" 946943402017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943404239","data":{"timestamp":" 946943404238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943407231","data":{"timestamp":" 946943407230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943409606","data":{"timestamp":" 946943409605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943411998","data":{"timestamp":" 946943411997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943415172","data":{"timestamp":" 946943415171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943417555","data":{"timestamp":" 946943417554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943419931","data":{"timestamp":" 946943419930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943422950","data":{"timestamp":" 946943422949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943425252","data":{"timestamp":" 946943425251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943427554","data":{"timestamp":" 946943427554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943430841","data":{"timestamp":" 946943430840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943433135","data":{"timestamp":" 946943433134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943435421","data":{"timestamp":" 946943435420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943438785","data":{"timestamp":" 946943438785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943441250","data":{"timestamp":" 946943441249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943443729","data":{"timestamp":" 946943443728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943446590","data":{"timestamp":" 946943446589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943448789","data":{"timestamp":" 946943448788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943450999","data":{"timestamp":" 946943450998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943454435","data":{"timestamp":" 946943454434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943456766","data":{"timestamp":" 946943456765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943459129","data":{"timestamp":" 946943459128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943462248","data":{"timestamp":" 946943462247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943464504","data":{"timestamp":" 946943464503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943466789","data":{"timestamp":" 946943466788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943469797","data":{"timestamp":" 946943469796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943471941","data":{"timestamp":" 946943471940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943474062","data":{"timestamp":" 946943474061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943477225","data":{"timestamp":" 946943477224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943479508","data":{"timestamp":" 946943479506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943481808","data":{"timestamp":" 946943481807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943485015","data":{"timestamp":" 946943485014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943487233","data":{"timestamp":" 946943487232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943489453","data":{"timestamp":" 946943489453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943492739","data":{"timestamp":" 946943492738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943495039","data":{"timestamp":" 946943495038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943497349","data":{"timestamp":" 946943497348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943500504","data":{"timestamp":" 946943500503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943502850","data":{"timestamp":" 946943502849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943505213","data":{"timestamp":" 946943505213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943508595","data":{"timestamp":" 946943508594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943508715","data":{"timestamp":" 946943508714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" d98d9252-c4a4-4a12-8c7a-2d7a35f82a31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943527250","data":{"timestamp":" 946943527250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943527634","data":{"timestamp":" 946943527633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943528127","data":{"timestamp":" 946943528127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943528480","data":{"timestamp":" 946943528479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943528893","data":{"timestamp":" 946943528892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943529380","data":{"timestamp":" 946943529379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943529614","data":{"timestamp":" 946943529614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943532820","data":{"timestamp":" 946943532820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943532857","data":{"timestamp":" 946943532857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943533583","data":{"timestamp":" 946943533582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943533990","data":{"timestamp":" 946943533989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943534296","data":{"timestamp":" 946943534295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943534508","data":{"timestamp":" 946943534508"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943534714","data":{"timestamp":" 946943534713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943535045","data":{"timestamp":" 946943535044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943535280","data":{"timestamp":" 946943535279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943538465","data":{"timestamp":" 946943538464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943538875","data":{"timestamp":" 946943538875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943540222","data":{"timestamp":" 946943540222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943540291","data":{"timestamp":" 946943540291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" cc12e30c-d0d6-414f-bc9f-fcf9164fb035"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943561747","data":{"timestamp":" 946943561747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" eupe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EUPE"," userResponse":" EUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943566131","data":{"timestamp":" 946943566131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" eupe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EUPE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943567670","data":{"timestamp":" 946943567670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943572992","data":{"timestamp":" 946943572991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943576341","data":{"timestamp":" 946943576340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943579102","data":{"timestamp":" 946943579102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" endesha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943580718","data":{"timestamp":" 946943580717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" erupe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ERUPE"," userResponse":" ERUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943583200","data":{"timestamp":" 946943583199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" erupe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ERUPE"," userResponse":" ERUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.44__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943585223","data":{"timestamp":" 946943585221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" erupe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943585340","data":{"timestamp":" 946943585340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" f1e91553-f537-41b8-a596-7dbbe99a07fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.44__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" erupe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ERUPE"," userResponse":" ERUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943603779","data":{"timestamp":" 946943603779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-m-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943607228","data":{"timestamp":" 946943607228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_l-e-g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943611163","data":{"timestamp":" 946943611163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_f-h-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943614750","data":{"timestamp":" 946943614750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_i-e-t"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943618472","data":{"timestamp":" 946943618472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_g-e-z"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943622000","data":{"timestamp":" 946943621999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_h-e-n"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943625331","data":{"timestamp":" 946943625331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-e-k"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943629121","data":{"timestamp":" 946943629120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_b-u-e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943632734","data":{"timestamp":" 946943632734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_e-t-m"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943636533","data":{"timestamp":" 946943636533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_d-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943642318","data":{"timestamp":" 946943642316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 30426885-fb7f-4eca-9385-4905c1a1b10d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_e_d-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943673248","data":{"timestamp":" 946943673248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_e_j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943679899","data":{"timestamp":" 946943679899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_v_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943686550","data":{"timestamp":" 946943686550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_l_s"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943693193","data":{"timestamp":" 946943693193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_l_p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943699859","data":{"timestamp":" 946943699859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_i_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943706543","data":{"timestamp":" 946943706543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_m_t_e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943713185","data":{"timestamp":" 946943713184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_e_p"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943719860","data":{"timestamp":" 946943719860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_b_a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943726511","data":{"timestamp":" 946943726511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_r_e_v"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943733113","data":{"timestamp":" 946943733113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_e_r"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943745206","data":{"timestamp":" 946943745205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 673cc974-6fc5-486f-8564-b3095f923528"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_i_e_r"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943764577","data":{"timestamp":" 946943764577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943765654","data":{"timestamp":" 946943765653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943772255","data":{"timestamp":" 946943772254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943773329","data":{"timestamp":" 946943773328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943776895","data":{"timestamp":" 946943776894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943777946","data":{"timestamp":" 946943777945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943781666","data":{"timestamp":" 946943781665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943782736","data":{"timestamp":" 946943782735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943786018","data":{"timestamp":" 946943786017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943787083","data":{"timestamp":" 946943787082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943790847","data":{"timestamp":" 946943790846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943791892","data":{"timestamp":" 946943791892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943795693","data":{"timestamp":" 946943795692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943796749","data":{"timestamp":" 946943796748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943802482","data":{"timestamp":" 946943802481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_024817"," gameId":" 5d5329f3-68f0-4c6a-a5a4-bbbe305f1d4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}